Hey, how's it going?
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for coming.
I appreciate you.
I really just more want to get an understanding.
When you say pro-criminal, what do you mean?
I mean that when confronted with people who have committed criminal acts, Donald Trump
has been either soft on them, friendly with them, pardoned them, and of course, let's
not forget, I mean, we've got five minutes left, I'm surprised it hasn't come up earlier,
he's a convicted criminal himself sitting in the White House.
Okay, I want to make sure I understand you correctly, because I don't want to strawman
you.
You're saying- I appreciate that.
Every time that he's been confronted- Not every time, I don't say the words every
time.
Most times.
A lot of the times.
Yes.
He's leaned towards criminal activity.
I didn't say criminal activity.
I mean, he has committed crimes.
He's been indicted for 88 different criminal offenses in four different jurisdictions by
five different grand juries.
He was convicted himself on 34 different criminal offenses by a jury of his peers, but let's
part that for a moment.
He's committed to his own crimes when confronted with the crimes of others, or the alleged
crimes of others.
For example, a Chinese crypto billionaire called Justin Sun, who was being investigated
for market manipulation.
Trump dropped the case, invited him to the golf course, invited him to the White House-
Plenty of examples.
And the guy invested $70 million in Trump's cryptocurrency.
That's pro-crime in my view.
Okay, so what I want to ask you is this.
Okay, so is it possible, because remember, the burden of proof's on you, right?
You have to prove.
Is it possible that all these things that he's done that supposedly make him pro-crime,
is there's another reason for the doing it?
Or is there other justification?
For example, let me give you an example and then you can rebut it.
The J6.
Yes.
Is it possible that he could have done this to unite the country, to move past, to go
to a new chapter?
If it's even possible, I think you would have to admit that there's another possibility,
therefore he's not pro-crime, at least in possibility.
So let me agree and disagree with you.
So I agree with you that the intent could be different.
I don't think Donald Trump was sitting there saying, how can I increase the level of murders?
Let me release some murderers.
Right, right.